mackie.com 2019-09-26

# Welcome to our Privacy Policy | Mackie

This policy applies to all information collected or submitted on Mackie’s website and our apps for iOS, Android, macOS and Windows, and any other devices and platforms.

**WHO WE ARE:**  
Mackie.com and Mackie apps for iOS, Android, macOS and Windows, and any other Mackie devices and platforms are operated by or on behalf of LOUD Audio, LLC (referred to as “LOUD”, “we”, “our” and “us”). LOUD’s registered address is: : 

LOUD Audio, LLC  
16220 Wood-Red Road NE  
Woodinville, WA 98072, USA  
+1 425 892 6500

**INTRODUCTION:**

LOUD provides you this privacy policy to explain to you how LOUD collects, uses and protects your personal information when you visit LOUD’s websites and when you use LOUD’s products and apps. LOUD respects your privacy and is committed to securing your personal information. This privacy policy was last updated on August 9, 2018. By using our website and apps, you consent to our privacy policy and acknowledge that it is subject to our Terms of Use. 

This policy applies to all information collected or submitted on Mackie.com and our software applications for iOS, Android, macOS and Windows, and any other devices and platforms.

**COLLECTING AND USING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION:**  
We collect the personal information that you provide to us, as well as information automatically collected when you interact with this website, such as cookies and analytics tracking pixels, which help us evaluate the performance of our website, provide you with a better user experience, and for customer support. 

LOUD may use your personal information that you provide to us in the process of establishing an account on our website in the following ways:

  1. Obtain your name for purposes of communicating with you and identifying you as a user of the website.
  2. Verify your age as older than 13.
  3. Verify your age as older than 18 or that you have obtained your parent’s or guardian’s permission to use the website.
  4. Verify that you are not subject to U.S. region-wide or individual sanctions that would prohibit LOUD from entering into any transactions with you.
  5. Send you a catalog.
  6. Send you communications upon your request.
  7. Allow you to participate in a promotion or other web site feature.
  8. Customize and/or personalize your communications and shopping experience with LOUD.
  9. Better respond to your customer concerns and complaints.
  10. Keep you informed of LOUD’s upcoming product releases unless you otherwise opt out of such messages.
  11. Technical, product, and warranty claim support

LOUD may use your personal information that you provide to us in the process of making a purchase in the following ways:

  1. Confirm your use of a valid credit card (or other authorized methods of payment).
  2. Process your payment via a credit card (or other authorized methods of payment).
  3. Send you the products that you purchased.

To fulfill your product orders, we may also disclose your personal information to our affiliates, third party service providers or distributors.  
LOUD also gathers non-descriptive, non-personal information about how many visitors use our website. LOUD does not collect any personal information about you in this instance but LOUD may collect information that a user has visited the website for statistical analysis of the public’s use of our website. 

**SOFTWARE AND APPS**

Mackie apps collect aggregate, anonymous statistics, such as crash reports and the percentage of users who use particular features, to improve the app. Some Mackie apps allow the creation of user images for channel, show or preset identification. These can be imported from the photo library or directly taken with the device camera. The user can manually export these images as part of show or system exports, which can then be reimported into the app. These images are not shared with Mackie.

Some Mackie apps allow recording from a devices microphone or digital audio inputs, and/or the playback of audio from a devices headphone, speakers, or digital audio outputs. The user can manually control when recording and playback occurs. These recordings are not shared with Mackie.

**UNSUBSCRIBING, REMOVING OR MODIFYING YOUR INFORMATION:**  
LOUD appreciates that you may change your mind about our use of your personal information in the future. LOUD offers several ways you can inform us about your privacy preferences:

  1. All email messages and newsletters will provide a description of how you can ask us to stop sending you messages and newsletters.
  2. At any time, you can send us an email at the address provided below.
  3. At any time, you can call our customer service number and request that you would like to change your marketing preferences.
  4. To modify or delete entirely the information you have provided during registration, please log in and update your profile.

Please note that if you have unsubscribed from our communications, you may still receive communications already in production until your request is fully processed. If you request that your registration information be deleted or if you unsubscribe from communications, we may maintain information about sales transactions or service inquiries for future service and record keeping purposes.  

**US-EU SAFE HARBOR PRIVACY STATEMENT**

LOUD is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of those who entrust us with their personal information. Our employees, and all those who do business with us, trust and expect that we will protect their personal information in accordance with the promises we make. In furtherance of our commitment, we comply with the U.S.-European Union Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>. 

**ONLINE TRACKING:**  
A cookie is a small removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. LOUD may use cookies to improve your experience with our website. LOUD may use cookies to improve LOUD’s understanding of your likes and dislikes about our website, what you like and do not like on our website, customize the website to your prior uses and to generally improve all customer needs and interests. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your web browser settings. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. You may also delete cookies from your computer.  

**DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURES:**  
The “Do Not Track” standard is still in development and not yet finalized. We will only collect and use the personal information you provide to us pursuant to the terms in this privacy policy. 

**DISCLOSURE AND SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION:**  
LOUD does not rent, sell or disclose your personal information or contact information to third parties for the third party’s own purposes. LOUD may share your information with LOUD’s affiliates under the same control of LOUD as permitted under this privacy policy. In the event LOUD is reorganized or transferred to a third party, your personal information may be transferred to the successor of LOUD for the purposes and subject to the terms of this privacy policy. LOUD (or, for consumers outside the United States, our distributor) may provide your credit card (or other authorized payment method) information to LOUD’s bank or credit card or other authorized payment processor solely for purposes of processing your payment. LOUD may also share your information with delivery services or international distributors to ship products to you. On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, or when required by law, to enforce our website policies, or to protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.  

**PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION:**  
LOUD engages the use of numerous technological security measures to preserve the security of your information, including without limitation, encryption technologies and authentication tools. Your personal information is contained behind secure networks and is only accessible to a limited number of persons who have a need to access your personal information for purposes of managing our website and providing you information as you have requested. All orders are placed through a secure server. Please be aware that no electronic data transmission over the internet can be 100% secure. 

**TRANSFERRING YOUR INFORMATION OVERSEAS:**  
If you are located outside of the United States, LOUD may transfer your information to LOUD’s affiliates under the same control as LOUD, to other service providers or distributors outside of your country or territory. LOUD manages its website from the United States. LOUD acknowledges that the data protection laws and other laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as those of your country or territory and LOUD will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights are respected. LOUD agrees to take the following actions on your behalf: have specific security measures in place to adequately protect your information, LOUD will require its United States-based affiliates to sign a contract guaranteeing the safeguard of your personal information and set forth the specific requirements the United States-based affiliate must maintain and monitor ongoing compliance with the defined security measures. 

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY:**  
We respect the privacy of children. Our website is not designed to attract an audience younger than 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. Please contact us using the contact details below if you believe we may have collected information from your child, and we will work to delete it. 

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS:**  
Under California laws, California residents can request information from LOUD whether LOUD has disclosed a person’s personal information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. LOUD will not sell or share your personal information with non-LOUD companies for their direct marketing purposes without your consent. California residents desiring to request further information about our compliance with these laws or have questions or concerns about our privacy practices and policies are welcome to contact us using the contact information below. We never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**OBTAINING A COPY OF OR UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION:**  
You can write LOUD at any time to obtain the personal information LOUD possesses about you or modify any personal information LOUD retains that is incorrect. Please let us know what information you would like to receive from us or what information is incorrect and we will respond to you. Your request should include your name and proof of your identity. 

**CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY:**  
We will notify you when we make any material changes or updates to this privacy policy, including any material changes in how we use or share your personal information. 

**QUESTIONS AND FEEDBACK:**  
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. 

**NOTICE AND CONTACT INFORMATION:**

For questions or concerns, please email us or contact us at: 

Via email:  

In writing:   
LOUD Audio, LLC  
16220 Wood-Red Road NE  
Woodinville, WA 98072, USA

© 2018 LOUD Audio, LLC

Date of Policy August 9, 2018

PDF of Current Policy
